# **Kevin Towner**

# Web Designer, Optimization

908.577.6666 kevintowner@gmail.com

### **Summary**

Product designer and digital optimization professional with over 10 years of experience in business operations and website design. Currently an MSI student at Drexel University, studying Human-Computer Interaction and web designer at AIG Travel Guard.

## **Experience**

Web Designer | AIG, Travel Guard 2022 - present

- Design and execute optimization initiatives for AIG partners such as United Airlines, Lufthansa, and Qantas
- Collaborate with TCS team on web authoring and segmentation within Adobe Experience Manager and Adobe Target
- Develop and maintain flexible component style guide for multiple partner panels by documenting CSS styles

Account Analyst | AIG, Op Services 2019 - 2022

 Document Op Services processes, and assist PCG with information gathering and workflow design

Business Services | AIG, Surplus Lines 2017 - 2019

 Processed quote requests and researched broker codes for appropriate underwriting assignments

Visual Manager | Hollister Co. 2014 - 2017

 Managed all seasonal floorsets, visual merchandising efforts, and in-store marketing placements

### **Volunteer**

Usability Analyst Historic Wyoming 1 month

 Volunteer opportunity where I helped the organization by conducting usability audits and heuristic evaluations on their website

#### **Skills**

#### **Tools**

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- HTML5 & CSS3
- Adobe Experience Manager
- Invision
- Qualtrics
- Useberry

#### General

- UI Design
- UX Research
- · Web Design
- Mobile Design
- · Usability analysis
- Design systems
- Website authoring
- Web optimization

#### **Education**

MSI Drexel University

· Human-Computer Interaction

**BA** Kean University

· Criminal Justice